Alien.
Should be a cult. Brain, I should be a rat to live
so little.
Should be a cult, alien.
Seven hours of silence Seven hours of her voice A
list of rules and warnings I didn't have a choice
The mountains rolling past the glass A world
I'll never know I'm just a passenger, I'm
trapped With nowhere else to go Uh huh.
Brute force 60 rolling west, a knot of panic in my
chest The engine is a pounding drum, from
everything I've overcome Or everything I'm
running to, I don't know what I'm going to do This
silly college experiment, I'll break before
I'm bent
She's watching me, I feel her eyes She thinks I'm
going to fail This trap she set, this college
test A cage outside the jail The road is long, my
hands are cold I wish that I could hide This car's
a cell, this angry hum With her right here inside
Route 460 rolling west A knot of panic in my chest
The engine is a pounding drum From everything
I've overcome Or everything I'm running to I
don't know what I'm going to do The silly college
experiment I'll break before I'm bent
I'm not ready.
She's right. I'll fail. I'm not ready.
Route 460 rolling west A knot of panic in my chest
The engine is a pounding drum From everything
I've overcome Or everything I'm running to I
don't know what I'm going to do This silly
college experiment I'll break before I'm bent
Eh